winster.com 2019-06-13

# Winster - Games, Friends, Prizes

Last updated: May 11, 2018

Seaside Entertainment, LLC. ("Winnie", "I", "we", "us", "our") believes in the Golden Rule: We respect your right to privacy, and intend to treat your personal information as We would want ours treated on your web site. This notice describes our Privacy Policy. 

By visiting Winster.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

Our Privacy Policy is intended to describe to you how and what data we collect, and how and why we use your personal data. It also describes options we provide for you to access, update or otherwise take control of your personal data that we process. 

If at any time you have questions about our practices or any of your rights described below, you may reach our Data Protection Officer ("DPO") and our dedicated team that supports this office by contacting us at privacy@winster.com. This inbox is actively monitored and managed so that we can deliver an experience that you can confidently trust. 

#### What personal information do We gather about you? 

**Information you give us** : When you sign up for Winster we may ask you for information such as your username, password, email address, address, date of birth or other demographic information. You may also choose to voluntarily add other information to your profile. We will store the information provided on our systems and use it for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We may receive and keep any information you enter on our web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our offerings.

**Information about you obtained from third parties** : In the course of our business, we may receive and keep information about you that we receive from third parties. This could include information from our business partners and/or vendors as to whether, when, and how you collect your prizes or make other purchases from them, package shipping status and delivery information, or other information that relates to or results from your relationship with us. We may consult sources of information related to your credit history or from credit bureaus, which we use to help prevent and detect fraud and to offer certain credit or financial services to you. 

**Automatic information** : We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our web site. For example, like many web sites, we use "cookies". We love many kinds of cookies, but these cookies are small files that we store on your computer that permit us to remember things about you, such as who you are and when you last visited. We may also allow third parties, such as our advertising partners, to place cookies on your computer. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. You can set most browsers to tell you when a new cookie is deposited, or to prevent cookies from being stored altogether. 

**Email and other communications** : When you email, fax, phone, write, or otherwise contact us, we may keep a record of these communications. 

To easily access, view, update, delete your personal data, or to update your subscription preferences, please sign into your Account and visit ?My Stuff?. Note that even though you change or delete your information on our web site, or cancel your account, we may keep copies of your information for our records or for backup. We may also retain certain credit and credit card information, for use in future audits, investigating charge backs, as required by merchant agreements or creditors, or for other legitimate business purposes. If you make a request to delete your personal data and that data is necessary for the products or services you have purchased, the request will be honored only to the extent it is no longer necessary for any Services purchased or required for our legitimate business purposes or legal or contractual record keeping requirements. 

#### Do we share what we know about you? 

In general, we only share information about you with third parties when we need to in order to transact business with you or on your behalf, when you have requested us or permitted us to, when required by law, when we think it will benefit you (i.e. for your own good), or occasionally, for our own profit. We may also share your personal information with you, when we reasonably believe we are communicating with you. 

In the course of running our Games and operating our web site, there are occasions when we may share information about you with other members and players. We will tell you that we may do this when we collect, or you provide us with, specific information such as your screen name and interests. 

We send you email and other forms of communication for a variety of reasons, such as to tell you about new games, features, and prizes, to tell you if you have won, to confirm orders and charges, to deliver prizes and gift certificates, and to respond to your customer service requests. Also, we may send offers to you on behalf of other businesses. If you do not want to receive certain email or other communications from us, send an email from the email account that you would like to remove to [unsub-int@winster.com](mailto:unsub-int@winster.com?subject=UNSUBSCRIBE) with "UNSUBSCRIBE" in the Subject field. 

We employ people, consultants, and other companies to perform functions for us. This may from time to time include order fulfillment, prize delivery, sending mail (postal and electronic), analyzing data, marketing consulting, processing credit card payments, providing customer service, and other business functions. These organizations and individuals may have access to your personal information as needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. Note specifically that we may share information about you with business partners and vendors from whom we source prizes, including gift certificates, and they may retain this information for their records, add you to their customer records, and treat this information in accordance with their own privacy policies which may differ from ours. we may receive discounts, payments, or other forms of consideration in return for sharing this information with them. 

As we grow our business, we may sell or buy other businesses, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the terms of any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, you give us permission to do otherwise). If our business (or substantially all of its assets in one or more transactions) is acquired by or assigned to another party, your personal information may be one of the assets transferred to that party. 

We also like to obey the law, so we may release your personal information as appropriate to comply with the law or in response to what we believe to be legitimate requests from law enforcement agencies. If we suspect that you aren't playing fair, have lied to us, are impersonating or pretending to be someone else, are violating the law or our Terms & Conditions of Use, are abusing our web site or are infringing our rights (or those of some third party) in some way, we may disclose your information to others in order to investigate our suspicions or help them to stop you from behaving badly. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction, among other purposes. 

Other than the above, we will tell you when we intend to share information about you with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to tell us not to do it. 

Special message for California Residents: Effective January 1, 2005, companies that collect personally identifiable information from California residents and disclose such information to third parties (including affiliated entities) for marketing purposes must, in response to a request by a consumer, either (1) provide a list detailing the categories of information shared and the entities to which such information was provided or (2) provide a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having their information shared with third parties (SB 27). We have elected the second option, and you may request that your information not be shared with third parties by sending or hand delivering your request, including your full name, email address and postal address to: Seaside Entertainment, LLC., | 2110 Artesia Blvd. Suite 101 | Redondo Beach, CA 90278. 

#### What do we do to protect your information? 

We are committed to handling your trusted information with high standards of security. 

We use scrambling (encryption) methods to protect precious information like credit card numbers. In fact some things (like passwords) are so scrambled that nobody, not even us, can unscramble it. 

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that protect your information. We restrict access to your information to employees who need to know that information in order to help you. 

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software when appropriate, which scrambles your information like an egg when it is transmitted between your computer and ours.

We maintain information on a computer that is not directly accessible from the internet. Instead, we keep it tucked away discreetly behind our cozy little firewall.

You can help! Anyone who has or gains access to your account will be able to view your personal information, so please be sure that you protect yourself by controlling access to your computer(s), keeping your login and password information confidential, and exercising care when using other people's or public computers. And watch out for those sneaky kids around the house - they know more than you think! 

#### Kids! Gotta love 'em (but not here)! 

We love kids, but not on our web site. As per our Terms & Conditions of Use, no one under the age of 18 can register on our web site or play our Games. 

#### Terms & Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions 

When you visit our web site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Notice and our Terms & Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, and application of the law of the state of California. Please contact Customer Support if you have and questions or issues about these policies. 

Our web site may contain links to other web sites, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

We always strive to improve ourselves and our web site, and so our Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions of Use may change from time to time without notifying you. We recommend that you check our web site once in a while to see if we have made any changes. 

#### Data Protection Authority.

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA) and believe we maintain your personal data subject to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you may direct questions or complaints to our lead supervisory authority, the German Federal Commisioner for Data Protection and Freedom of Information (Die Bundesbeauftrafte für den Datenschutz und die Informationsfreiheit), as noted below: Husarenstraße 30 53117 Bonn, Germany Phone: +49 228 997799 0; +49 228 81995 0 Fax: +49 228 997799 550; +49 228 81995 550 e-mail: poststelle@bfdi.bund.de
